affsphere.com 2010-12-03

# Privacy And Policy

Thank you for visiting AffSphere.com, a site owned and operated by Affiliate Classroom, Inc. AffSphere's Privacy Policy falls under under the Privacy Policy of the Affiliate Classroom, Inc. ("Affiliate Classroom") personal data management and e-commerce Internet web site ("Site") located at the URL www.affiliateclassroom.com. The Privacy Policy below details certain policies implemented throughout Affiliate Classroom's sites, governing Affiliate Classroom's use of personally identifiable information provided to Affiliate Classroom via this Site, plus privacy policies specific to your use of AffSphere.com. 

### Privacy Policy Updates

Due to the Internet's rapidly evolving nature, Affiliate Classroom may need to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. If so, Affiliate Classroom will post its updated Privacy Policy on our Site located at www.affiliateclassroom.com, as well as on AffSphere.com, so you are always aware of what personally identifiable information we may collect and how we may use this information. Affiliate Classroom encourages you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of this Site will be subject to the then-current Privacy Policy.

### Information Collection and Use

You can generally visit AffSphere without revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself. However, to use certain services of AffSphere, we may require you to register for an account, or we may invite you to submit questions or comments or request information, participate in surveys, questionnaires or contests, subscribe to newsletters or participate in community forums. 

Due to the nature of some of these activities, we may ask that you complete and submit an online form with personally identifiable information such as your name, username, email address, contact information and credit card information. The reason we ask for this personally identifiable information is so we can deliver the services, products or information you have requested, create a user account for you, verify your authority to enter password protected areas of AffSphere (such as your author account), send you notices for products and/or services that you have used or that may be of interest to you, and improve the content and general administration of AffSphere. 

If you are a registered user of AffSphere or Affiliate Classroom, Inc. and post content to the article database or community forums, other registered users of AffSphere or Affiliate Classroom, Inc. may view your username and may send you emails, but they will not be able to see your actual email address. 

We may occasionally use your personally identifiable information to send you advertisements and other promotional information regarding our products and services, or the products and services of our third party marketing partners, and other communications related to the AffSphere and Affiliate Classroom, Inc.

### Children's Privacy

Affiliate Classroom recognizes the privacy interests of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's online activities and interests. AffSphere and Affiliate Classroom and Affiliate Classroom's services are not intended for children under the age of 13. Affiliate Classroom does not target any of its services or sites to children under the age of 13. Affiliate Classroom does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13.

### Cookies

We may use small digital files called cookies to improve your overall experience of AffSphere. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a user's hard drive containing information about the user. Cookies generally do not permit us to personally identify you. You may need to enable cookies in your browser to use certain areas of AffSphere. 

Advertisements that appear on AffSphere are delivered to users through our advertising partners. Our advertising partners may download cookies to your computer. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement. In this way, they may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. This information allows an advertising network to make sure sales are tracked correctly and to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. AffSphere and Affiliate Classroom, Inc. do not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers.

You may, if you wish, remove third-party cookies from your computer at any time. To manage cookies when using the AffSphere site, remember that if you use different computers in different locations, you will need to adjust the browser settings according to your cookie preferences. Also remember that in order to use some of the features of AffSphere, you will need to enable cookies. 

You can delete cookies that have been installed in the cookie folder of your browser. In Firefox, this can be done by clicking Tools | Clear Private Data. Be sure the "Cookies" box is checked, then click "clear Private Data Now." If you are using Microsoft Internet Explorer, how you manage and clear cookies depends on the version you are using. Microsoft has a comprehensive page which explains how to handle cookies, and delete them here: http://support.microsoft.com/kb/278835

### Aggregate Information

AffSphere may track the total number of visitors to our site, the number of visitors to each page of our site, IP addresses, External Web Sites (defined below) linked to, and we may analyze this data for trends and statistics in the aggregate. But such information will be maintained, used and disclosed in aggregate form only and it will not contain personally identifiable information. We may use such aggregate information to analyze trends, analyze traffic, administer the site, track users' movements, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We may share this aggregate information with third parties to assist them in targeting advertisements to appropriate audiences.

### Disclosure

We may need to provide your personally identifiable information that we collect and the data generated by cookies to the vendors and service agencies that we may engage to assist us, for example, we may provide your personally identifiable information to an organization in order to complete a service such as processing your payment. We will also disclose your personally identifiable information if we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority. We will not sell your personally identifiable information to any other company or organization, except that we may transfer your personally identifiable information to a successor entity upon a merger, consolidation or other corporate reorganization in which Affiliate Classroom participates or to a purchaser of all or substantially all of Affiliate Classroom's assets to which this site relates.

### Links to Third Party Sites

AffSphere may provide links to other Web sites or resources over which Affiliate Classroom does not have control ("External Web Sites"). Such links do not constitute an endorsement by AffSphere or Affiliate Classroom of those External Web Sites. You acknowledge that AffSphere and Affiliate Classroom are providing these links to you only as a convenience, and further agree that AffSphere and Affiliate Classroom are not responsible for the content of such External Web Sites. Your use of External Web Sites is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies located on the linked to External Web Sites.

### Security

We may employ procedural and technological measures, consistent with industry practice.  Such measures are reasonably designed to help protect your personally identifiable information from loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction.  Affiliate Classroom may use encryption, secure socket layer, firewalls, internal restrictions, password protection and other security measures to help prevent unauthorized access to your personally identifiable information.

### Correction/Updating Personally Identifiable Information

Affiliate Classroom provides you with the ability to review, correct and delete any of the personally identifiable information that you have provided to us.  If you wish to review or correct any information you have provided to us,

  * You may access your account and review, correct and delete your personally identifiable information
  * Or you may contact us through our [support desk](http://www.affiliateclassroom.com/eSupport/).

**If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy please contact us:**

**Affiliate Classroom, Inc.**  
387 Technology Drive  
Suite 3119  
College Park, MD 20742

301-314-5832 (Phone)  
301-314-5833 (Fax)  
[Click here](http://www.affiliateclassroom.com/eSupport/) for the Support Desk to contact us via our email ticket system.

This Privacy Policy was last updated: May 21, 2008  
This Privacy Policy is effective as of: May 21, 2008
